i'm about to interview two of the richest men
in the entire world and i'm not talking billionaires
no no no no are you a millionaire i'm
not a millionaire but according to forbes i'm a
billionaire does forbes lie i don't know but
that's not all because like i said i'm gonna
be interviewing not one billionaire but two
of them so you're a billionaire yes multi-billionaire
what was the most amount of money that you made
in a single year november 1st 2021 that's the day we
sold body armor to coca-cola for eight billion
dollars and that was the most money that ever
came into my account at one time and the
craziest part you guys most people go their entire lives
without ever speaking to a billionaire and in
this video i'm gonna be meeting up with and
interviewing two of them in less than one hour but
before we do that you guys since i'm in a literal
billionaire hub out here in florida i'm gonna be
hitting the streets to go and find the hidden
wealth that is out here in one of
the richest states in america listen the real billionaire
secret is there's no secret you set out to
make 100 grand and then you make a billion
this video is about to be insane from start
to finish so stay tuned until the end with
that being said come with me to meet some billionaires
excuse me sir sir is this your rolls royce yes and
how did you get a rolls royce what did you do to
become wealthy all these beautiful buildings around
here with all these great retail tenants
yes that's what i do i own and
operate retail shopping centers throughout the state of florida
how long have you been in real estate for 28
years over these 28 years what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year november 1st 2021
that's the day we got our first billionaires in a
year i'm not going to tell you that did you give
me a raise no more than 10 million dollars a lot more
more than 100. i'm not going to tell you they're
gonna get me kidnapped i go all over the world i
go all over the world and even millionaires and
billionaires can i get one minute with you for
our channel absolutely let's do it how much real estate
do you own now i own a lot of real estate
do you think the home is a good investment
the home is a terrible investment the home is not
an investment but a lot of people would disagree with
that though right i get that all the time and
i argue this point with people over and over and i
actually own a home and i can tell you it's the
stupidest investment you could make it is not
an investment neither is this car it's not an
investment it's a luxury item you want to have and i
could take you back over time and i could take you
back over time homes don't always go up in price
the problem is most people that are 40 years old
and younger have never seen a bad real estate
market i've lived through them and by the way
homes do go down in price so somebody
has a hundred thousand dollars saved up right now
where would you put that money in today's world
i'd go right into a commercial property i'd find
an asset class you like the truth is multi-family is
the easiest one to get into you can buy a
duplex a triplex put a hundred thousand dollars
down you can easily buy a three four hundred
thousand dollar property you need to manage it
yourself you need to lease it yourself you need
to take care of it running all the books yourself
learn the game fix it up keep it going then
eventually you can refinance it pull some cash out of
it and you can get a good deal out of it
out of that and go buy another what's the best
time to buy real estate always the best time to
buy real estate always always the best time to buy
real estate what about in a bad market always the
best time if it's a bad market it's a good time
to buy and if it's a good but good market it's a
good time to buy you always want to
be buying real estate why because it's generational and
if you're not going in with the flip this is
not like wholesaling and trying to get in and out
if you're going in and saying i'm going to buy
this property and i'm going to keep it for 10
20 30 years it's always a good time to buy and
by the way nobody can time a market so you can watch
all the stuff you want in the news all the
stuff you want in the newspapers none of it's right
if anybody you live only own real estate you'll
be drag cannot be real estate for a long time
If anybody really knew, they'd
be the richest man on earth.
And one of them, Warren Buffett, will tell
you all the time, he can't time anything.
What's your name?
Todd Napola.
Todd, the majority of Americans
are living paycheck to paycheck.
What keeps people broke in today's world?
Lack of financial education.
You know, I was never a great student in school, but the schools
simply do not teach you what to do when you get out of school.
They teach you how to be good at
history, math, science, and so on and so forth.
They teach you how to get into college, but they don't teach you how to get a mortgage, how to balance a checkbook, what
to do with credit card debt, what's good debt, what's bad debt, why you should be buying a business, not buying a damn jet ski.
That's what they don't teach you.
So let me ask you this.
If you can instill one money lesson in every
person watching this video right now, what would that be?
Don't listen to the masses.
The masses are entirely wrong.
The masses are going to tell you the right thing to
do is to save in your 401k and your IRA account.
It's going to tell you to buy a house and pay it off in 30 years
and hope you get a job with possibly a pension and you're going to be okay.
You won't.
Take care of yourself.
Be financially responsible.
Did you ever have anybody that doubted you in business?
Oh, yeah.
You're going to have a lot of doubters, but doubters don't
necessarily doubt you because they don't think you could do it.
They're just afraid you might do something that they're
not doing, and then they got to hold themselves accountable.
And that's a big problem for people.
So don't worry about what people tell you.
No.
Do your own thing.
Stay in your own game and keep chugging forward.
What did you learn
about entrepreneurship that surprised you?
It's way better to be an entrepreneur.
Most people think it's scarier, but it's way better
to be an entrepreneur than to work for someone else.
Do you think everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
Oh, no.
I think a lot of people think they are, but when you find
out what it's like to be the boss, it's not always that much fun.
How old are you now?
And if me and you died tomorrow and you could leave
one more guiding principle to the younger generation, what would that be?
What worries me for your generation specifically, I have
two daughters your age, is this image that's out there.
And everybody's competing against a non-government.
It's a non-existent thing.
What I mean by that is you guys are seeing guys,
especially in Miami, Lamborghinis at 20 years old and living in penthouses.
Everybody has a penthouse in Miami.
There's not that many, but
everybody seems to live in one.
And there's an illusion that it's so easy
and everybody has it and they give themselves stress.
And you know what I'm going to tell you?
I have a guy in my office who I let borrow
one of my cars because he wanted to bet with me.
It's a joke.
And he literally took pictures of the car
and he posted a picture of himself on Instagram.
And the other day he was
down and I'm like, what's wrong?
He's like, everybody's doing better than me.
I see it all over Instagram.
And I said, you're that guy.
You didn't put in your post, that's my car.
You're doing the same thing.
It's just an illusion.
Nobody gets there quick.
Yes, there's going to be some rich kids, but whether you're going to be the best lawyer, the
best architect, the best real estate guy, whatever it is, it's going to take a lot of time.
So don't count other people's money.
Don't compare against them because remember,
comparison is the thief of joy.
As long as you're making forward progress
and having fun, it's going to be great.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you so much for your time.
It's been a lot of fun.
Guys, I just interviewed one of the
richest real estate entrepreneurs in the country.
And I want you all to understand something right now.
Look, I've interviewed over $25 billion.
The richest people on the planet.
And you know what they all have in common?
Every single one of them,
they all invest in real estate.
But here's the crazy thing, you guys.
Next week on Monday, September 22nd, I'm
doing something that I've never done before.
I'm going to be hosting the first ever
real estate day inside of my private entrepreneur community.
I'm hosting three back-to-back workshops covering the topics that you
need to know to create and build wealth in real estate.
The three workshops are going to be taught from
some of the richest real estate entrepreneurs on the planet.
And they're going to be covering.
How to buy real estate
with little to no money down.
So that way, even if you have no money,
you can figure out how to buy real estate.
They're also going to be breaking down these smartest
strategies to build passive income through real estate investing.
So you can learn how
to make money while you sleep.
And lastly, they're going to be breaking down how to
find, fund and flip properties, even if you're starting from scratch.
But you guys want to know
the craziest part about real estate day?
Do you know how much it's going to cost you to come learn
from three of the most dominant real estate investors in the entire world?
It is completely free to join.
You are literally going to be able to learn from.
And ask for free.
Your specific questions directly to some of the
richest real estate tycoons in the entire world.
They're going to be mentoring you directly and for free.
Understand this, you guys, the way to get rich in today's world is to learn directly
from the people who've already built empire and do exactly what they tell you to do.
Implement those strategies to build wealth in real estate.
So to get access to real estate day this next week and
access to the number one most powerful entrepreneur community in the entire world.
All you have to do is go down,
click the link in the description of this video.
To join the community for free and get
access to real estate day this next week.
I can't wait to see you there.
With that being said, let's get back to the video.
All right, so guys, we're right now actually going to be
linking up with John Morgan, billionaire lawyer, the richest lawyer in America.
You guys, he built one of the largest law firms in the
entire world, and we're going to be meeting up with him again.
You guys saw our interview that we did with him
the first time, but it's time to run it back.
We're in his city.
We're going to be getting the blueprint from him on what it takes
to become a billionaire and one of the hardest industries in today's world.
There he is.
What's going on?
I thought they were going to send some rum-dum
to do the questions, and you'd be coming from Austin.
Absolutely, man.
It's you yourself.
Yes, sir.
It's good to see you.
I know since last time, our video
got like 60 billion views because of you.
Is that why you're back?
That's why I'm back.
And they need some more billionaire secrets today.
Listen, the real billionaire secret is there's no secret.
You set out to make 100
grand, and then you make a billion.
Who am I here with today?
I'm John Morgan.
Are you a millionaire?
I'm not a millionaire, but
according to Forbes, I'm a billionaire.
Does Forbes lie?
I don't know.
They don't lie.
How did you make your billions?
I built the largest personal injury firm in North America.
So was the sacrifice worth it to become a billionaire?
It wasn't a sacrifice.
Why not?
The journey is the reward.
It was all fun.
I wasn't looking to get rich.
I was just looking to build a business.
And then you wake up one day, and
you're an old man, and here you are.
I asked you in our last interview,
have you ever been fucked over before?
And I told you, yes,
I have, but I fucked back.
I know you like that.
Now, there's over 8 billion people
on planet Earth, and there's only like 3,000 billionaires.
What's the one thing that you
did differently from 99.999% of other people?
Look, I don't know.
And people who say they do are lying.
It works like this.
It's a bunch of left turns,
right turns, U turns, backing up.
And all of a sudden, it ends up here.
One bad turn, one wrong turn.
It's all different.
So I don't pat myself on the back.
I don't say, hey, John, you're great.
Drop me in the city, and
I'll be a billionaire in a month.
No, I go, thank you, God,
for letting me have this great life.
Now, take me back to the
most life changing conversation you ever had.
What is the greatest advice
you ever received throughout your career?
The most important person in my
life was a guy named Bill Dimitri.
He built things all over Florida.
I gave the eulogy at his funeral.
And the other thing he told
me that I never forgot was this.
John, the money does not belong to you.
The money belongs to God.
And if you remember this, this
world is going to end like this.
And on our last day, we're not going to
be talking about money or what deal we didn't do.
We're going to be talking about
and thinking about the time we didn't
spend with the people we love.
Money is important, but at a
certain point, it's not that important.
As a billionaire, would you consider yourself to be smart?
I am not smart, and I know
I'm not smart, which is very good.
But I'm smart enough to know I'm not smart,
and I'm smart enough to hire people who are smart.
I read a book once called Tight about Rockefeller.
And in that book, they said he built Standard Oil.
And somebody asked him, how
can you build this oil company?
You're not a scientist.
You're not a geologist.
You're a bookkeeper.
And here's the line I underline.
I hire scientists.
I'm not a smart guy, but I'm smart
enough to go find smart guys and girls.
So the richest people in the world, they bring
other people in to do the task for them.
Look, Steve Jobs, he didn't build Apple.
Was built it.
You know who the billionaire is?
Jobs.
You know who the billionaire is not?
Was was was the genius of Apple, not Steve Jobs.
How many people watching this even know who
I'm talking about when I say was nobody?
But everybody knows who Jobs is.
How important is it to
surround yourself with the right people?
Look,
one time a guy named
Bill McBride was running for governor.
He was head of Holland and Knight, big law firm.
And he told me this.
Your children are one friend away from total disaster.
And if you don't separate it when
you see it, you could lose your kid.
And twice during my children's lives, I cut off two different
children from coming to our house or going to their house.
It's hard to do because your kids
are like, what are you talking about?
That's my friend.
But we know better than our kids at that age.
And it's hard to do.
But what's harder to do is to let your
kid go down that road and end up like this.
That kid.
And they completely fuck up their lives.
Listen, when you lay and sleep with
pigs, you get pig shit on you.
You cannot sleep with pigs
and get up without pig shit.
That's from my brother, Tim.
How can somebody connect with a billionaire?
Read a book called Never Eat Alone.
If you're just going to sit at your desk and not get out in your comfort zone, if you're not going to
have lunch, you're not going to go to a convention, if you're not going to network, you're not going to do shit.
Luck doesn't just come.
Luck comes when you're looking for opportunity.
If you're not looking for opportunity, you're going.
Not.
Nowhere fast.
There's a lot of people like
a gerbil on a spin wheel.
They're running the fuck all day long.
At the end of the
day, oh, my God, I'm exhausted.
Hey, you went no fucking where?
You got to leave the cage.
You got to get outside.
You got to come around.
Hey, I'm at this convention.
I'll speak here.
I'll go there.
I'll go to the happy hour.
I'll network.
You're not going to make money or find opportunity or luck or blessings or
whatever you want to call it in the cage running on a spin wheel.
If I took everything away from you and all you could
keep is one trait, one skill set, one mindset to become
a billionaire, make it back, what would that be?
Keep your word and hire great people and share.
Listen, the great circuses are built.
The Ringling Brothers, Barnum and Bailey.
You see these little bullshit circuses
around with a seal limping around.
The reason that Ringling Brothers,
the greatest circus ever, was this.
The people came to see the lion and
the tiger eat the man in the middle.
You know why they don't
eat the man in the middle?
Because he loves them and feeds them.
If you're building a business, think about the guy in the ring and
why the lions don't eat him because he loves them and feeds them.
And when you see the great Walenda up on the
wire walking without a net, you know why he didn't fall?
Focus, focus, love them and feed them.
You got amazing advice, man.
This is awesome. Thank you, John.
Guys, we just interviewed the
billionaire lawyer, John Morgan, once again.
He just gave us a masterclass.
But as promised, you guys, I told you I was
going to be interviewing two billionaires in less than an hour.
And that's exactly what we're going to go do.
We're about to head out right now to go meet up
with an interview with the multi-billionaire, Mike Rapoli, at his house.
Guys, the time has now come.
We just got to Michael Rapoli's house.
Or should I say one of
his houses out here in Orlando, Florida.
And he lives, as you can see,
at an absolute compound out here, you guys.
But it's as expected.
Guys, he's one of the
richest men in the entire world.
He sold not one but two companies to Coca-Cola, one of
the biggest companies in the world, for billions of dollars, you guys.
So I'm calling it right now.
This is going to be one of
the craziest interviews that I've ever done.
I guarantee you he's got the likelihood to give me more game than just
about any billionaire or anybody that I've ever interviewed for that matter, you guys.
So let's go meet Michael right now and go
see what he has to say for you guys.
Come on.
Michael, what's going on, my friend?
How are you doing?
Hey, come on.
It's great to meet you.
Thank you for having us out.
Yeah, I appreciate it.
First of all, you've got
a nice compound out here, man.
This place is incredible.
Yeah, this is my guest home.
We were letting them know, right, some billionaires
make their fortune off of oil or tech.
But you built $2 billion companies out of drinks that most
people have had in their fridge at one point or another.
Yeah, I did it the consumer package goods way.
Small order and vital order from 98 to 2007.
Sold that to Coke for $4 billion.
And then in 2011, started another.
The sports drink called
Body Armor competed against Gatorade.
And we sold that in 2021 for $8 billion.
Combined, two companies to Coke for $8 billion.
Did you think growing up all this was possible?
You know, I always said, think big, dream bigger.
If you're hitting your dreams,
you're not dreaming big enough.
My dreams are bigger now than
they were when I was 15.
Now, I got one rule for today's interview.
There's no holding back.
You give them the secrets and the blueprint on
what it takes to become a billionaire in today's world.
Can we make that happen?
Can they handle it?
We're going to have to find out.
Let's fucking go then.
What's more important, product or distribution?
Always the product.
The product, the consumer.
The distribution.
To me, it's the least important.
The least important.
I'll tell you why.
But Warren Buffett says distribution
is the key to everything.
Well, Warren Buffett's 95 years old.
Micropoli's 55 years old.
There's a big difference.
And that's why he's an investor in Coca-Cola.
His company, buy my company.
So I thank Warren for approving two
deals of my companies to Warren Buffett.
Do you think it's better to
be an investor or to start businesses?
Because investor, it's not as intensive.
Entrepreneurship's hard, man.
You've got to eat shit for a long time.
Well, but being an investor, you don't control anything.
You control that guy's decisions.
I want to bet on myself.
If you're a real entrepreneur,
you don't bet on other people.
You bet on yourself.
Did you ever doubt yourself?
I never doubted myself, but I
knew I was going to lose.
Did you have people that doubted you?
Everybody.
And by the way, not always in a negative way.
My mom and dad told me to be careful.
You know, they were immigrants coming from France.
My dad was a waiter.
My mom was a seamstress.
So when I was making big money just
having a job, you know, at a water company,
and I said at 28 years old, I
want to go partners with this guy, Darius Bykoff,
and holy, I want to do this.
They said, oh my God, be careful.
I took a pay cut to start my own company.
I took a pay cut to be president.
And I was president of a $100,000 company.
But it grew to $750 million,
and we sold Coke for $4.1 billion.
Let's go back to distribution one.
At the end of the day, distribution is just a
delivery agent or a way to get product out there.
If you build a product that consumers
demand, you don't have to worry about distribution.
Those accounts are going to call you for your product.
My customers are asking you
for your body armor sports ring.
Then you know you created the
demand, and they come to you.
Let me ask you this.
Did you come from a lot of money?
Yeah, my parents were worth about $5,000.
I lived in a two-bedroom apartment with six people.
I slept in the same room
with my brother for 28 years.
We became a New York City cop, which you
couldn't pay me $20 million a year to do that.
My mom and dad were in the next room, and
my grandmother and my aunt slept in a pull-out couch.
And we had one bathroom and a
beautiful shower curtain, and that was it.
So you didn't come from money.
How did you get the money to start your business?
At the end of the day, when you're
only a $100,000 company, you're looking at $10,000.
I took money from friends, family.
My partner had money.
We put it all together.
And at the end of the
day, we didn't try to grow quick.
That's the other thing.
We did $100,000 the first year.
Second year, we did $500,000 at Vitamortar.
Then we did $1 million.
Then we did $3 million.
Then we did $9 million.
Then $32 million.
Then $50 million, all the way to $750 million.
Body armor was the same thing.
It went from $1 million to
$1 billion and sold for $8 billion.
So it's starting slow.
If you want to build a billion-dollar company,
you have to build a $100 company first,
then a $1,000 company, then a
$100,000 company, then a million-dollar company,
then a $10 million company.
So it's not going to happen overnight.
And that's the biggest thing.
Everybody says, oh, I want to be an entrepreneur.
I want to be successful.
I want to be rich.
But I spend more time talking
people out of being an entrepreneur.
Because this is what I say.
First five years for an
entrepreneur, I call the survival years.
Every single day.
You could go bankrupt.
There were days that I
didn't think we could make payroll.
Did you almost fail?
No, I failed.
I failed every time.
But what is the definition of failure?
Going bankrupt?
No, we didn't do that.
But having a bad sales month or bad day or
lose $2 million and have to find a way to survive?
Yeah.
So failing is good.
If you don't fail in
life, you're not trying hard enough.
I fail more than anybody
that's ever failed in the world.
I love failing.
Failing means I've taken as far as I can, and now I've
got to figure out another fucking way to get to the next level.
If you're not failing, that means you've
got a lot more in the tank.
I'm finding out at 55 years old.
I still have.
I still have a lot more in the tank.
I'm happy.
I'm not content.
Once you get content, you might
as well just give it up.
But you've already sold two businesses for
billions of dollars, and you're not satisfied.
Why not?
Because there's a lot more to do.
There's things to do with your family.
There's things to do with your friends.
There's things with businesses.
At the end of the day, what you find out is that whether you're a great basketball
player or a great coach or a great musician or a great athlete or a great entrepreneur,
at the end of the day, you think you're
competing against the outside or you're competing against people.
That's really just noise in your head.
You're just competing with yourself.
There's a great poem out there.
Everybody should.
I read this called Man in the Glass.
At the end of the day, if you're happy
with yourself, you're going to have a great life.
If you're miserable with yourself and everybody loves
you, you're going to have a miserable life.
So to me, it's me versus me.
I'm competing against myself.
So Mike Rapoli at 55 is competing
with Mike Rapoli at 45 and 35.
My goal is to be better every day or
even worse sometimes, suck less every day and push myself.
The guy that pushes me the most is Mike Rapoli.
The guy who pushes Tom
Brady the most is Tom Brady.
The guy who pushes Kobe
Bryant the most is Kobe Bryant.
Not his teammates, not his coaches.
People who are great have
to live up to their expectations.
They're tough.
They're on themselves and they are their teammates.
So at the end of the day, it's your level.
As long as you know that you're competing against yourself
and you want to be great, you should never be content.
Happy is great.
Content is boring.
Most billionaires I've met have lost their minds.
Are you a little crazy?
I started crazy.
So it's not lost your minds.
First of all, I think everybody's crazy.
I talk about mental illness way different.
It's got this stigma.
Everybody has something.
Everyone gets a little anxiety.
Everybody has a little stress.
Everybody has a little ADHD.
It's okay.
Everybody has it.
So if everybody just goes out there and
says, hey, I have it and you have it.
Now, there are people who have it at different levels.
And a lot of people that try to hide
their mental illness is why it gets out of control.
Because the harder it becomes to
hide, the worse it can get internally.
But I am crazy.
I mean, if you ask my
wife of 25 years, I'm crazy.
If you ask my family, my friends, I'm crazy.
If you ask me, I'm crazy.
But there's nothing wrong because
crazy people change the world.
And crazy people have big dreams.
I don't want anybody to be as crazy as me.
Trust me.
But I do want people to take
chances and get a little crazier in life.
And be a little bit more adventurous.
And take chances.
And don't be afraid to fail.
How old are you now?
I'm 55.
Mike, if me and you died tomorrow and
you had one more message for the younger generation,
what would that be?
Oh, man.
Live life to the fullest.
Live every day like it's your last.
And one day you'll be right.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you, man.
Thank you so much for your time.
You guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
I need you all to like and
subscribe for amazing content coming every week.
Because nobody's doing this, you guys.
We just brought you guys
several multi-billionaires back-to-back for you all.
And guys, if you have
not already done so, go down.
Click the link in the description of
this video to join the School of Mentors.
It's the number one, the most
powerful entrepreneur network in the entire world.
Where I give you guys
direct access to the multi-millionaires.
And billionaires I interview on
this channel every single week.
Where you ask your questions directly to them.
And they mentor you directly.
Guys, I literally give you access to
my millionaire and billionaire friends every week.
All you have to do is go down.
Click the link in the description to join.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said, we'll
see you in the next video.